They say the past always catches up with you. This could be the day.
Thursday is a thriller, action, comedy film directed by Skip Woods.
A former Los Angeles drug dealer moves far away to Texas, making a new
life for himself as a married architect in the suburbs.
His old crime partner unexpectedly shows up with heroin and gangster
business, attracting a slew of violent unsavory characters.
Casey Wells, played by Thomas Jane.
Christine, played by Paula Marshall.
Nick, played by Aaron Eckhart.
Billy Hill, played by James LeGros.
Dallas, played by Paulina Porizkova.
Dr. Jarvis, played by Michael Jeter.
Thursday is a 1998 American black comedy crime-thriller film written and directed by Skip Woods and starring
Thomas Jane, Aaron Eckhart, Paulina Porizkova, Paula Marshall, Michael Jeter and Mickey Rourke.
It won the Special Jury Prize at the Cognac Festival.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.